question_data = [
    {"category":"Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the play Oedipus Rex, Oedipus kills his father due to jealousy in loving his mother.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Assyrian king Sennacherib&#039;s destruction of Babylon in 689 BCE was viewed as a triumph by other Assyrian citizens.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Bulls are attracted to the color red.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The man that shot Alexander Hamilton was named Aaron Burr.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Full Metal Panic!, Whispered are those who are capable of creating Black Technology.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]
    }]

